pearson.com 2017-07-06

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Pearson collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each a "User" or "you") of the www.pearson.com website ("Site"). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all the services offered by Pearson on this Site.

## Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Site, subscribe to email alerts, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site-related activities.

## Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance Users' experience. A User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert them when cookies are being sent, but this may result in some parts of the Site not functioning properly. For more information please see our Cookie Policy.

## How we use collected information

**Pearson may collect and use Users' personal information for the following purposes:**

  * _To improve Users' experience_  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site and so that we may improve our Site.
  * _To send periodic emails_  
If the User decides to opt-in to our email alerts, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.  

## How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

## Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personal identification information to others. We will not allow unrelated third parties to use your personal information for marketing without your consent.

We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We may disclose and share personal information with the third parties listed below. Because the internet is a global environment, you accept and agree that this will include the transfer of your personal information to other countries around the world, including countries outside of the European Economic Area which may not have the same data protection laws as the UK. 

**We may share your personal information:**

  1. with our group companies or any entity which acquires any part of our business
  2. with our service providers (including, for example, suppliers who develop or host our sites or who operate mail list services for us)
  3. with third-party search engines that may index user profile pages and usernames as part of the URL of the user profile page by default
  4. if required or permitted by law
  5. with other third parties with your consent.  

## Changes to this privacy policy

We may update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this Privacy Policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. You acknowledge that this website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that Pearson has no control or influence over the privacy practices of such other sites.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site, or your dealings with this Site, please contact:

Data Privacy Office  
Pearson plc  
80 Strand, London WC2R 0RL, UK
